[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unforgettable character did actor Heath Ledger portray in the 2008 Batman movie The Dark Knight?", "correct_answer": "The Joker", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman", "Two-Face", "Robin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pygidium refers to what section of a trilobites body?", "correct_answer": "The tail", "incorrect_answers": ["The head", "None of these", "The thorax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which set of numbers is most significant to baseball?", "correct_answer": "3,4,9", "incorrect_answers": ["1,83,26", "9,13,26", "1,7,17"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is used for the preparation of the French delicacy Escargot?", "correct_answer": "Snail", "incorrect_answers": ["Oyster", "Shrimp", "Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name this small tree also known as the Apalachin, whose leaves are used to prepare a strong infusion that contains large amounts of caffeine.", "correct_answer": "Yaupon", "incorrect_answers": ["Calamus", "Wild Fennel", "Sweet Sedge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fingerprints of the baby begin forming in this week of pregnancy. The baby also starts grasping and sucking its thumb at this time.", "correct_answer": "18th", "incorrect_answers": ["21st", "35th", "10th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinctive feature is characteristic of the crocodile species called gharial, or Indian gavial?", "correct_answer": "Narrow snout", "incorrect_answers": ["Very short tail", "Red spots on its back", "Purple scales"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In mathematics, 6!\u201d is read as six factorial\u201d. Calculate 6!", "correct_answer": "720", "incorrect_answers": ["24", "120", "21"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors starred in Rob Reiners 1992 movie A Few Good Men?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "Bruce Willis", "Denzel Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Adventures in Babysitting what is the last name of Chris, the main character played by Elisabeth Shue?", "correct_answer": "Parker", "incorrect_answers": ["Smith", "Jones", "Thompson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cardinal Richelieu, the bad guy in many of the works of Dumas, was a brilliant minister for which king?", "correct_answer": "Louis XIII", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis XVI", "Louis XV", "Louis XIV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who discovered the gyroscope effect, now used for measuring orientation?", "correct_answer": "Johann Bohenberger", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas A. Edison", "Leon Foucault", "Booker T. Washington"]}]